你的第一次是跟女人做？
So your first sexual experience was with a woman?
我那年15岁 跟最好的朋友露丝在一起
I was 15. It was my best friend,Ruth.
苹果酒太烈，我们醉了
And we got drunk on that hard cider.
一不注意，我们已经在亲热了
And then suddenly,we were making out.
再说一次
Tell it again.
我是认真的
Seriously.
那个女人就只会聊性爱吗？
Can that woman talk about anything else but sex?
不会啊，她刚才在聊地理
Yeah,sure. Earlier she was talking about geography.
她在列举她做过爱的国家
She was listing the countries she's done it in.
大家都学到了一些东西
I think we all learned something.
各位，看我找到什么
Hey,you guys! Look what I found!
那是我妈的笔迹，看
That's my mom's writing. Look.
“我、弗兰克与菲比 1965年毕业典礼”
"Me and Frank and Phoebe,graduation,1965."
知道其中的含意吗？ 你已经50岁了？
-Do you know what that means? -That you're actually 50?
那个菲比不是我，是她的朋友
That's not "me" Phoebe. That's her pal,Phoebe.
毕业纪念册上说她们是BFF
According to her yearbook,they were BFF.
永远的莫逆之交
Best Friends Forever.
太棒了
That's great!
我知道，她八成知道 我父母的事情
I know! She probably has all kinds of stories about my parents.
甚至知道我爸的下落
She might know where my dad is.
我找过了，她住在海边
I looked her up. She lives by the beach.
我们这个周末可以去海边
Maybe this weekend we can go there.
讨厌，我得工作 太可惜了
-Shoot,I can't go. I have to work. -That's too bad.
真是扫兴
Big fat bummer.
那我们明天开车去莫陶克
So tomorrow we'll drive out to Montauk.
邦妮在那里做过
Hey,Bonnie had sex there!
本集播出：“在海边”
The One At the Beach
乔伊马上下来，他在找他的面罩
Joey will be right down.He's looking for his mask.
-游泳面罩？ -不，他的猩猩面具
-A swim mask?-No, his gorilla mask.
他戴着那个在海里吓唬鱼
He wears it in the ocean to scare off the fish.
你看他们
Would you look at them?
我再也交不到男朋友了
I'm never gonna find a boyfriend again.
我会变成老姑婆
I'm gonna die an old maid.
你不会变成老姑婆
You're not gonna die an old maid.
可能会变成老厨娘
Maybe an old spinster cook.
谢了 如果万不得已
-Thanks. -Besides,worse comes to worse...
我会当你的男朋友
... I'll be your boyfriend.
是啊
Yeah,right.
有什么好笑的？
Why is that so funny?
你是在开玩笑吧？
You made a joke,right?
所以我笑了
So I laughed.
笑得太厉害了吧
A little too hard.
我不适合当男朋友吗？
Am I not boyfriend material?
你是钱德
You're Chandler.
你知道嘛，钱德
You know. Chandler!
我们确认了我的名字 还打了我一拳
Okay,so we've established my name,and hit me.
如果我们不是朋友 如果是个盲目的约会
But say we weren't friends. Say it's a blind date.
我来到你家门口，说 嗨，很高兴认识你
I show up at your door and I'm,like,"Hey,nice to meet you."
我会害怕用假嗓子说话的人
I'd probably be scared of a guy using a fake voice.
真好，你买了吃的
Oh,good. You bought food.
不是，这是我的行李
No,just my luggage.
我这个星期有最好的运气
I am having the best karma this week.
我找到认识我父母的人
I find this woman who knew my parents...
我的客人又把海滩小屋借给我
...and then my client gives me his beach house.
被你打的自行车快递员呢？
What about that bike messenger you hit?
我不是在说他的运气
Oh,I wasn't talking about his karma.
看看这顶帽子
Hey,check out the hat!
慢着，我认得那顶帽子
Wait a minute,I know that hat.
我被戴上那顶帽子
I was taken aboard that hat.
它们对我做实验
They did experiments on me.
我不能生育了
I can't have children!
说真的，那是哪来的？
Seriously,where did you get the hat?
罗斯送的
Ross gave it to me.
我觉得她戴起来很好看
I think she looks good.
是他买给你的
Did he buy it for you...
还是为你赢来的？
...or win it for you?
很抱歉，这位时尚白痴
Excuse me,my fashion-impaired friends...
帽子又流行回来了
... I'm here to tell you hats are back.
这一回它们聚集成 一顶超级大帽子
And this time,they've ganged up and formed one giant super-hat.
快快快
Go,go,go!
现在你们又想躲到帽子底下
Now everybody wants to be under the hat!
怎么这么多沙子？
What's with all this sand?
鲍伯说可能淹过水
Bob said there might be flood damage.
不然就是他有一只很大的猫
Either that or he has a really big cat.
你们知道这让我想起了什么吗？
You know what this reminds me of?
我为什么不能做你男朋友？
Why couldn't l be your boyfriend?
你还在想那件事？
Are you still on that?
-你能不能不要谈这个了？ -谢谢乔伊
-Would you let it go already?-Thank you, Joey.
但是你会跟我约会的，对吧
But you'd go out with me, right?
不，情况跟钱德一样，我们是朋友
No. lt's the same as with Chandler.We're friends.
让我们假设我们是这个星球上最后的两个人类
Let's say that we were the last two guys on the planet...
并且有一把枪对着你的脑袋，你选哪一个？
...and you had a gun to your head.Which one would you pick?
你们哪个拿着枪对着我的脑袋？
Which one of you has the gun to my head?
这个房子不太一样
It's kind of an unusual house.
有三个漂亮的卧房，没有浴室
It has three beautiful bedrooms and no baths.
但是大海就在旁边
But,you know,the ocean is right there.
有人在吗？
IKnock,knock,knock.
请等一下…请进
Hang on. Come in,come in.
你考虑完再打给我
Think about it and call me back.
你是菲比艾博特吗？
Are you Phoebe Abbott?
吃惊吗，菲比！我是你的最好的朋友的女儿
Surprise,Phoebe Abbott! I'm your best friend's daughter!
你是尔文的女儿？
You're lrwin's daughter?
是以前的最好的朋友，你看
I mean your old best friend. Here.
高中的莉莉，记得吗？ 天哪，莉莉
-Lily? From high school? Remember? -Oh,God,Lily. Yes.
我当然记得莉莉
Of course I remember Lily.
那你一定是…
Then you must be
菲比 菲比
Phoebe,Phoebe.
应该是取自你的名字
She named me after you,I guess.
看，是弗兰克
Wow. Well. Look,there's Frank!
对！没错！
Yeah! Yes! Yes,yes!
那是我爸爸弗兰克
That's my dad. That's Frank!
抱歉我这么激动
I'm sorry I'm getting all flingy.
别激动，那里有饼干
Take it easy. If you want,there's cookies.
或者桑格里厄汽酒！我去准备桑格里厄汽酒
Or sangria! I could make sangria!
不用，饼干就行了，谢谢
Sorry. Cookies are good,thanks.
总之，我一直在找我爸
Anyway,I've been looking for my father.
你有他的消息或见过他吗？ 没有，对不起
-Have you heard from him or seen him? -Oh,no,I'm sorry.
我毕了业就跟大家失去联络
I lost track of everybody after high school.
那就把我父母的事都告诉我，全部的
Well,so tell me everything about my parents. Everything.
你也知道，我们总是形影不离
Oh,well,you know,we were always together.
其他人帮我们取了个绰号 什么绰号？
-The other kids had a nickname for us. -What was it?
三个失败者
The Three Losers.
可怜的莉莉
Oh,poor Lily.
我听说她的事了 你一定非常难过
I heard what happened. That must have been just terrible for you...
就这样失去母亲
...Iosing your mother that way.
不会啊，很棒
Yeah,no,it was great.
知道下雨天玩什么最好？
You know what a really good rainy-day game is?
我指的是裸体游戏
I mean,naked game.
我们应该来玩脱衣扑克牌
We should play strip poker.
你疯了吗？
Are you crazy?
拜托，出门一定要玩这个 这是一种规定
Come on. When you go away,you have to play. It's,like,a law.
那不是规定
Well, it's not a law.
只要它还是属于那个纳税改革议案，它就永远都不是
As long as it stays attached to that tax reform bill, it never will be!
好了 谢谢
-All done. -Thank you.
下一个是谁？
Okay. Who's next?
不行
No way!
拜托啦，我好无聊 你让我涂过一次
Come on,please. I'm bored. You let me do it once before.
如果这是本周末的规定…
Well,if that's the rule this weekend....
走开 大方一点，来
-Get away. -Take it like a man. Come on!
大坏人
Big bullies!
怎么样啊？
How are we doing?
无聊和无聊
Bored and bored.
玩脱衣扑克牌最不无聊
You know what naked card game's never boring?
菲比是什么样的人？
So what's Phoebe like?
我心肠好又体帖，莫妮卡呢？
I'm kind,caring and sweet. What's Monica like?
我是说你去找的那个菲比
No,the other Phoebe. The one you went to see?
我觉得她知道我爸的下落
I think she knows where my dad is!
太好了
Cool!
他在哪里？
Where is he?
她假装没有他的消息
She was pretending she hasn't heard from him...
但是我发现这张照片
...but I found this picture.
他现在不就应该长这样？
Isn't this what he would look like now?
很像
Totally familiar.
她为什么要骗你？
Why would she lie to you?
我们明天要吃晚饭 也许她到时会告诉我
We're having dinner tomorrow. Maybe she'll tell me then.
也许她想给他一点时间…
Maybe she just wanted to give him time...
帮我买礼物
...to buy me presents. I don't know.
你们都很无聊？
So you're all bored?
我闭上眼睛随便指 被指到的人
I'll close my eyes and point to someone. Whoever it is...
要想一件好玩的事 大家就一定要做
... has to think of something fun to do. And we have to do it.
好，散开来
Okay! Fan out! Fan out!
知道吗，我们也可以玩这个
You know,we could just do this!
我们要玩脱衣扑克牌
We all have to play strip poker?
为什么，突然，你想玩脱衣扑克牌？
Why, all of a sudden,do you wanna play strip poker?
我想是因为玛格丽特（鸡尾酒） 三杯、四杯和九杯
l think because of margaritas three, four and nine.
脱衣欢乐时光游戏？（改编自同名电视剧的大富翁游戏）
Strip Happy Days Game?
我找不到扑克牌 不然就随便脱着玩
I couldn't find cards,so it was this or Strip Bag-Of-Old-Knitting-Stuff.
好
Done.
“方奇（《欢乐时光》的主角）给了你两个手指，你得到两分”
"Fonzie gives you two thumbs up. Collect two cool points."
累积到五分 就可以叫别人脱一件衣服
Get five points,you get to make someone take off one item of clothing.
还没人脱，但是我们很兴奋
It hasn't happened yet,but we're very excited.
来吧
Okay,come on.
我要为史前辩论 赢一台电子显微镜
Daddy needs a new electromagnetic microscope for Prehistoric Forensics.
“带粉红托斯卡罗（《欢乐时光》的角色）到机会点”
"Take Pinky Tuscadero up to lnspiration Point.
“你得到三分”，漂亮！
Collect three cool points." Yeah!
我有五分了
Which gives me five.
我看看，谁要脱衣服啊？
And let's see,who is gonna lose their clothes?
我选本游戏的发起者 乔伊崔比亚尼先生
I think I pick our strip poker sponsor,Mr. Joey Tribbiani.
放激动，只是一只鞋
All right,relax. It's just a shoe.
“你的乐队在阿诺德表演 你得到三分”
"Your band is playing at Arnold's. Collect three cool points."
所以我有五分 乔伊要脱四角裤了
Which means I have five and that means I get Joey's boxers.
好，来对付我啊
Fine. Gang up on me.
我会让你们脱得很难看
I got you all,right where I want you.
快脱
Come on! Take them off!
其实有点冷
Actually,it's kind of cold.
我能不能不要脱 让你们瞄一眼就好？
What if I keep them on and give you a peek at the good stuff?
我再去调玛格丽特
I'm gonna make more margaritas.
你干什么？想把我灌醉？
What are you doing? Trying to get me drunk?
我只是要调玛格丽特
I'm just making margaritas.
我去帮忙
Think I'll help her out.
这是怎么回事？
What is going on here?
什么？
What?
你涂他的脚指甲，追着他跑
You're painting his toenails. Chasing him around the room.
莫妮卡，拜托
Monica,please.
他也跟你打情骂俏
He's totally flirting with you too.
没错吧？
He is,isn't he?
不晓得，也许是因为来到海边
I don't know. Maybe it's just being here at the beach together...
感觉上…
... but it's like something
邦妮
Hi,Bonnie.
老板提早放人 我就搭火车来了
My boss let me off early,so I took the train.
你们在干什么？
What are you guys doing?
玩脱衣欢乐时光游戏
We're playing Strip Happy Days Game.
酷，我来赶进度
Cool! I'll catch up!
你还是不觉得我…
So you still don't think...
适合当男朋友？
...I'm boyfriend material?
昨晚我发现你在打量我
I saw you checking me out during the game last night.
你连裤子都没脱
You didn't even take off your pants.
算你走运
Lucky for you.
什么？ 我不晓得
-What? -I don't know.
大家都开心吗？
Well,is everybody else having just the best time?
乔伊睡着了
Joey's asleep.
他睡过去 我们用沙子帮他保暖
He passed out. We put sand around him to keep him warm.
那对快乐的情侣还没起床吧？
Well,I assume the happy couple isn't up yet?
你们昨晚有听到吗？
Did you guys hear them last night?
我不知道他们在干什么 但是海龟一度爬进屋里来
I don't know what they were doing,but sea turtles came up to the house.
早安
Good morning.
睡得好吗？ 很好
-How'd you sleep? -Great.
跟木头一样
Like a log.
我们也是
Us too.
我要去散步
I'm going for a walk.
早安，好丰满的胸部
Good morning. Nice breasts by the way.
你怎么没来？
Hey,what happened to you?
没什么，我想在这里看书
Oh,nothing. I just felt like hanging out and reading.
海水好舒服，我们跳下桥墩 我的泳衣掉了
The water was so great. We jumped off this pier and my suit came off.
可惜我错过了
Sorry I missed that.
乔伊和钱德好有意思
Joey and Chandler sure are funny.
我的头发里都是沙子
I brought back half the beach in my hair.
以前光头方便多了
It was easier when I shaved my head.
我一定要告诉你
You know,I gotta tell you...
我好喜欢你光头的样子
...I just loved your look when you were bald.
真的？
Really?
我有考虑重新剃光头
I think about shaving it again sometimes.
真的？
Really?
你应该那样做
You definitely should do that.
我是该那样做
You know what? I should do it!
谢谢你，你好酷
You know what? Thank you. You are so cool.
别这么说
Oh,stop. Go on.
去剃光头吧 好
-Now go shave that head. -All right.
-我记得我以前问过你这个问题 -一百次了
-l know l've asked you this before.-A hundred times before!
-我怎么不适合你？ -我不知道
-How am l not right for you?-l don't know.
我喜欢像理查的男生
l like guys like Richard.
或者彼特，在他疯之前
Or Pete,before he went insane.
我不知道，是更成熟的人吧
l don't know.Just somebody more mature.
所以我是对你来说不够成熟？
So l'm not mature enough for you?
莫妮卡需要更成熟的人
Monica needs somebody more mature.
怎么了？
What's the matter?
她取消了，我同名的人取消了约会
She canceled. My namesake canceled on me.
她说她得进城去，她在躲我
She claims she had to go out of town. She's avoiding me.
她不想说出我爸的下落 她知道却不说
She doesn't want to tell me where my father is. She knows!
菲比好差劲喔
Pheebs,that sucks.
别跟我说差劲
Well,don't "Pheebs,that sucks" me yet.
你要去哪里？ 她出门了
-Where are you going? -She's out of town.
她家里一定有我爸的线索
Something in her house will tell me where he is.
有人称这种行为是擅闯
Some people call that "breaking and entering."
这里有人这么想吗？
Well,are any of those people here?
我会做一些好事
Look,I'll do something nice,okay?
我会帮她把制冰盒加水，好吗？
I'll fill her ice trays. Good?
嘿，各位
Hey,everybody!
看看你干了什么
Look what you did!
你想摸吗？
You wanna touch it?
不想，但是很不错
No,but it's great.
来嘛，摸嘛
Come on,touch it.
可以摸得到头骨
You can feel all the bones in your skull.
我刚和邦妮聊了一下 你猜怎样？
I was having a little chat with Bonnie,and guess what?
她提到整件事的幕后主使
She brought up who was behind the head-shaving idea.
是谁呢？ 对了，就是你
And now,who was it? Oh,that's right. It was you!
是她自己想剃
That was her idea.
我只是给了她建议
I just gave her a nudge.
她说你拿剃刀给她
She said you gave her the razor.
有人要去夜泳吗？
So anyone up for a midnight dip?
我不要 不了
-No,I'm good. -No,thanks.
待会见 好好玩
-Okay,I'll see you in a bit. -Okay,have fun.
拜托，看到了吗，她看起来也没那么糟嘛
Come on,see? She doesn't look that bad.
你能看到她的头反射的月光
You can see the moonlight bouncing off her head!
你在想什么？
What were you thinking?
我不知道
I don't know.
你让我女朋友变成光头
You balded my girlfriend!
好啦
All right.
看你跟别人在一起 难道我就好过？
Do you think it's easy for me to see you with somebody else?
是你要分手的
You're the one who ended it!
因为我很气你 不是因为我不爱你了
Because I was mad at you! Not because I stopped loving you!
你还爱我？
You still love me?
你还爱我
You still love me.
怎样？
Yeah,so?
你也爱我
You love me.
什么意思？
What does this mean?
你想复合吗？
I mean,do you want to get back together?
不是！也许吧
No! Maybe!
我不知道
I don't know.
我还是无法原谅你的行为
I still can't forgive you for what you did.
但是有时和你在一起 我会觉得…
But sometimes when I'm with you,I just feel so....
怎样？
What?
我会觉得…
I just feel....
我… 怎样？
-I just -What?
我觉得…
I feel
我不管
No! I don't care!
我不要跟你练习一对一脱衣扑克牌
I'm not playing one-on-one strip poker with you for practice!
牌都做好了
But I made cards!
晚安
Good night.
我要上楼去了
I'm going upstairs.
晚安 晚安
-Good night. -Good night.
要不要练习脱衣扑克牌？
Wanna play strip poker for practice?
我的屁股
My ass!
是我！
Oh,it's me! It's me!
我不想发出声音。-那就不要闯进来
-I didn't wanna make any noise! -Then don't break in!
对不起。-你来干什么？
-I'm sorry! -What are you doing here?
我来帮制冰盒加水
I came to fill your ice cube tray.
什么？
What?
好，是这样的
Okay,look.
这是从你的冰箱上拿的 我认得这是我爸爸
I took this picture from your fridge. I know that this is my father.
这是弗兰克布菲 你站在他身边
This is Frank Buffay,and you were standing next to him!
我有权利知道我的身世
I deserve to know where I came from.
要是你能帮我找到爸爸 你就应该帮我
So if you can help me find my father,then you should.
否则你就是坏人
Otherwise,you're just mean.
把真相告诉我
So just tell me the truth.
好
All right.
照片上的人是查克曼吉欧尼（著名爵士乐手）
The man in that picture is Chuck Mangione.
我爸是查克曼吉欧尼？
My father is Chuck Mangione?
他跟你没有关系
That's just Chuck Mangione.
我去年卖给他一栋房子
I sold him a house last year.
抱歉，我真的不晓得 你父亲的下落
And I'm very sorry,but I really don't know where your father is.
这是实话
And that's the truth.
但是你说得对
But you're right.
人有权利知道自己的身世
I think a person should know where they come from.
所以我…
Which is why l....
我是你的母亲
I'm your mother.
我昨天就想说，但是我…
I wanted to tell you yesterday,but I just...
我太软弱
...felt all floopy,and....
你们肯定要复合了
You guys are getting back together.
她自己都搞不清楚
She doesn't even know what she wants.
瑞秋还在气那件事
Rachel's still mad at me.
那就退出 你不需要受这种伤害
Then you gotta back away. You don't need that kind of hurt.
听我的话，我…
Take it from a guy who's...
从来没跟别人长期交往过
... never had a long-term relationship.
我知道，但我真的 很想上楼继续吻她
I know,but I really want to go up there and finish that kiss.
水好舒服，你们应该去游泳
The water is great. You should go in.
谢了，我刚吃了M&M牌巧克力
No,thanks. I just had an M&M.
晚安
Well,good night.
Good night.
早点上来
Don't be too long.
没问题
Okey-dokey.
真是一根毛都没有啊
There is not one hair on that head.
头发会长回来 而且她很风趣，很棒
It'll grow back,right? And she's really fun,and she's cool.
我终于往前走了
And I'm finally moving on.
要忘掉瑞秋实在…
Getting over Rachel was so
我终于恢复理智，要是我上楼
I'm finally feeling sane. And if I go up there...
吻了她…
...and I kiss her....
天哪，我好想吻她
God,I want to kiss her!
要是失败呢？ 我真的想再心碎一次吗？
And it doesn't work out. Do I wanna put myself through that again?
我想问一下
Let me get this straight.
选择邦妮是明智的决定 可以抛开过去
If you go with Bonnie,you do the smart,healthy thing and move on.
对吧？要是选择瑞秋 邦妮今晚是不是就空下来了？
Right? And if you go with Rachel,Bonnie's free tonight?
你好
Hi there.
你的声音又怪怪的了
That's that weird voice again.
再试一次
Let me try it again.
你会跟下一个人约会的，我发誓
You'll wanna date this next guy,I swear!
我现在只能用这个声音了
l can only do it with the voice now.
好吧好吧，关上门
Okay, okay.Close the door!
你好，我是小矮人
Hi,I'm Dorf!
你今晚的男伴
Your date for the evening.
拜托，小矮人约会耶 多有意思啊
Oh,come on. Dorf on dating? That's good stuff!